# Lora Spasova- Bachvarova

#### **Pharmacist**

Philadelphia, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Lora-Spasova--Bachvarova/0fe6f7300b2d9f95

Licensed Pharmacist in Pennsylvania with twenty years of experience in retail setting. Outstanding interpersonal skills with establishing positive relationships with customers, medical professionals, healthcare organisations and insurance providers. Dedicated to provide quality patients care, fast and accurate medical dispensing.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Pharmacist**

CVS Health - Philadelphia, PA - 2005 to Present

- prepared and dispensed prescriptions in busy retail pharmacy
- counseled patients of the use of prescription drugs and OTC products
- consulted with physicians regarding drug side effects and drug interactions
- entered patients and prescription information
- contacted with insurances regarding prior authorization
- called insurance companies to resolve insurance issues
- ordered medical supplies
- inventory management

## **Owner of the Pharmacy**

Pharmacy "Lora" - 2000 to 2005

managed and organized pharmacy network

- supervised three staff pharmacists and seven technicians
- consulted patients regarding prescription medication, dosage forms, side effects and interactions
- cooperated with physicians and hospitals regarding patient profiles and medication use
- controlled inventory
- offered a safe and desirable place to work for employees

## **Pharmacy Director**

City Hospital - 1994 to 2000

- Clinical monitored patients and collaborated with physicians to developed clinical use of medications and drug therapy
- Planned and approved cost saving programs, billing and reimbursement issues
- Supervised pharmacy team
- Supervised educational programs for the pharmacy
- Interacted with other hospitals regarding patients treatment
- Resolved insurance issues
- Planned pharmacy revenue

## **EDUCATION**

#### Master's Pharmacy in Pharmaceutical Science

National Association of Board's of Pharmacy - Philadelphia, PA

## **Master's in Pharmaceutical Science**

Medical Univercity - Sofia

**SKILLS** 

Computer, Retail, Management, Languages, Leadership

CERTIFICATIONS

CPR

**Medication Therapy Menagement** 

**Immunization Certification**